CLAUDIA GUERRA

QUALITY ASSURANCE | ASPIRING WEB DEVELOPER

claudiagbak@gmail.com | Leeds | Right to work in the UK | in claudiaguerrabak

@ claudiaguerrabak.netlify.app

ABOUT

A Quality Assurance Professional with 5 years of experience. Recently completed an intensive Web Development program, adding skills in HTML, CSS, React and more to software testing expertise. Organised and methodical, with an eye for detail, logical thinking, strong communication skills, and a solid work ethic.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Quality Assurance Consultant at Oracle

August 2022 - April 2024

Worked in the implementation of Energy&Water products such as C2M, CCS, and CC&B. Participated in different stages of testing, such as System Testing, Regression Testing, System Integration Testing and User Acceptance Testing. My main activities consisted of the following:

- Test execution, design and planning, as well as maintaining existing test cases
- Identification, documentation, and tracking of defects using Jira
- Implementation of new projects in collaboration with software development and design teams
- Creation of training materials, templates, and simulations to accelerate new employee onboarding

Software Validation Tech at Intel

January 2015 - October 2017

- Manual and Automated test cases execution for Intel Graphics, focusing on display, media, and rendering components
- Identification, documentation, and tracking of defects using Jira
- · Creation of comprehensive documentation for new platforms and training material on testing procedures
- Participated as point of contact for Android projects, utilising Linux environments

EDUCATION

Frontend Developer

May 2024 - October 2024

Junior Achievement Americas

Programming Foundations, Web Design, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and React.

Bachelor's degree in Physics

August 2023

University of Guadalajara (Universidad de Guadalajara), Mexico

CERTIFICATIONS

Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Certified Foundations Associate

2023

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner (In progress)

2024

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• HTML5

• CSS3

- Git & GitHub
- Bootstrap
- Jira

SOFT SKILLS

- Attention to Detail
- Teamwork
- Communication
- Proactive
- Adaptability
- Leadership

LANGUAGES

- English C1
- Spanish Native